PLEASE READ THIS BEFORE ANY USE OF THE FONT."EASTER" IS A FONT DESIGNED BY UNCARVINGLICENSE: GENESIS CAN BE USED EVEN FOR COMMERCIAL PURPOSES 
YOU MAY NOT SHARE THIS FONT, NEITHER ON WEBSITES OR TO OTHER COMPUTERS,UNLESS UNCARVINGS PERMISSION IS GIVEN.IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE AGREEMENTS, DO NOT INSTALL OR USE THE FONT. DISTRIBUTION IS NOT ALLOWED   ©UNCARVING, 2021DESIGN AND ARTWORKS BY UNCARVING / ALFIANUNCARVINGSKIIFY74@GMAIL.COM(+62)81229421972 (INDONESIA)